Hi. In the previous version, we used a course sort of one to build an application.
So, we also know that we use the MOOC API Red.
So, it's actually only for today,
but in one day, in one week, it won't be extra anymore.
And it would be nice to use the wife RedData.
We can fetch it from API.
To get always up-to-date results,
okay, let's wish our application.
The first is always you can keep all if you like the changes.
It will be stored and then after you ask for new changes,
you always have an updated difference like what was updated.
I can close the plan.
So, in this version, we will do two things.
First, we will ask a course or about some components and investigation of what API external services we can use
for getting the live rates.
And the next, we will ask a course or to implement it.
So, I already prepared the prompt,
but I will use Ask mode because we're not going to change something to just an investigation.
So, I'm asking what are the most popular external currency exchange rate APIs for JavaScript?
Please compare them with pros and cons and also highlight once which does not require API.
Because if an API require an API key,
it means we need to register, we need to create API key, it might be paid, so I want really easy integration.
So, let's ask a course or and see what investigation he wrote down.
We also can enable, of course, connect to browser, then he will search at the internet.
Not only is the mortgage based, so guess of my bits and other tool, okay.
Okay, we must use current series JavaScript, we have about 10 APIs.
So, the first one is open exchange rates, it requires API key, I will look at this parameter initially,
just don't spend the time if it's not a browser criterion.
And the next fixer is also required, current supplier, also required API key, exchange rate API, same XE currency data, same alpha advantage.
I never heard about it, of data, how much new exchange rate was, if they are not required,
the case, fine, output are not required, and European Central one, also not required.
Free official now also daily only URL based menu and points, okay.
Only in the else, so API, with examples, how to use them, so I need to make my choice between the three.
Okay, it's preparing API, those exchange rate that was no key, case the integration looks really simple.
Here, the transition by default, that place, so I'm going to create a bunch of data, ACB data only, it means it's used on the European Central bank data,
so it has some limited currencies, but for testing purposes it's fine, same, it also looks easy.
Okay, this one is source page, it's XML, you parse and build it on, okay, it's not a good one because it used XML, so JSON and points.
Okay, let's now quickly check this to, at the internet, just to make a quick choice.
Okay, so the exchange.post, I see it's free, but it's requiring API key, okay, so AI doesn't have access to latest information,
or it was just lazy, didn't search the internet, okay, we can ignore this one, and this one, no usage or API key.
Okay, it looks fine, it's a port, a URL, some base currencies, so it updates about four, it's fine, I guess it's fine for us, so we can use this one.
Okay, I already have a prompt, yeah, I will ask replace the mock exchange rates with the front footer API and this application and updates the UI to show the converted results from the API.
So I will ask him to leave the mock data, the rates, and use the actual ones and always get it from API, but I will use agent mode because I need to make changes.
And from this investigation, you can see how I did it, I used ask mode, I first ask about all apps, then pass some criteria.
Then I choose the three looks more of us fine, I ask about more details, then I filtered only two, and then I visited the URL websites, just double check if it's really a pass my criteria or not.
Okay, and if it's implemented, it also makes a small plan, you see like some bigger changes, course or make plan by default, yeah, you have some to do.
And current data updates the rates, and what we have.
Okay, it's decided to make an API request in this file, okay, it's also fine for me, yeah, it's good, it's updating the application.
So let's see what changes he will do, he update, and they'll swap and do convert.
Okay, he finished.
So let's check.
We'll refresh my page, and I try to convert use g2 euro, for example, 500.
Yeah, it did the fetch, so we can check, we can inspect, we can open network pop, and did it again.
Yeah, we see it requested the euro rate with a base currency use here, so it was a days date, so it's great.
I would say it works, so we can keep all changes, I will quickly review, yeah, we have an API instead of mod data, we still have more currencies.
Yeah, so it's fine. Now we know how we can implement some feature requests using kulsorii, and in the next lesson we will do an improvement, so don't miss it.
See you in the next lesson.